sudoku-web.net 2019-04-05

# sudoku-web.net - Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To help protect your privacy we are providing this notice to outline our information practices and how your information is collected and used.

The Information We Collect and How We Use It

For ordinary use of sudoku-web.net, consisting of playing Sudoku on our website, we only see your IP address, browser information and some cookies. Each is explained below.

When viewing any website, your web browser sends your IP address and browser information to the server for that site. Your IP address may provide an indication of the country or state where you are located, and your method of connecting to the Internet. Your browser information will probably include your browser name, operating system, version and language. Your IP address and browser information are not personal to you, and we cannot identify you from this information.

When you visit sudoku-web.net, our servers may send one or more cookies to your computer. A cookie is a short string of characters which your browser sends back with any subsequent requests to our site. Cookies enable us to store your game history and preferred options, and help us track usage patterns over time. Cookies do not enable us to identify you personally or learn about your use of other sites.

Our servers may record parts of the above information in their log files, in order to help us track usage of sudoku-web.net and improve our services. These log files are stored on secure servers in the Japan.

Third Party Services

Some features of Web Sudoku, such as the forum and tutorials, rely on a service provided by a third party. The advertisements shown on our website are displayed by third parties. We may also use a third party to analyze the traffic on our website. In these cases, the third party will also see your IP address and browser information, and may use cookies to track your usage over time.

Before entering any personal information into a third party website, you should check their privacy policy and ensure you are comfortable with their use of your information.

Your Choice in Providing Information

For ordinary use of sudoku-web.net, consisting of playing Sudoku on our website, we do not request any personal information. You may therefore choose not to use those features on our site which request information you do not wish to provide.

If you are uncomfortable with our use of cookies, you may use your browser settings to remove and block all cookies from sudoku-web.net at any time. You may also set your browser to confirm or reject all cookies received, to track or prevent the use of cookies by third party services.

Information Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have appropriate electronic and managerial procedures in place to safeguard and secure all information.

Accessing or Correcting Your Information

Upon request, we will make good faith efforts to inform you of any personal information we have stored, and correct or delete this information as desired. We will ask you to identify yourself and the appropriate information before fulfilling such as a request.
